<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
  <categories>
  </categories>
  <apps>
  <app id="8-ip"><name>8Zip</name><version>2.1.0.75</version><icon>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/draydenthemiiyt-maker/10-Store/refs/heads/main/files/SmallLogo.targetsize-48-1777635788.png</icon><publisher>Finebits OÜ</publisher><featured>false</featured><description>Out with the old, in with the new. The powerful archiver 8 Zip has expanded its set of capabilities with the new Continuum, Cortana and Windows Hello technologies.&#13;
&#13;
Now one app, one license, a uniform design and functionality can be had on all types of devices. Decrypt files through an iris scan or at a touch. Listen to music, read documents, and watch videos right in the app. Share files with friends – it’s simple.&#13;
&#13;
8 Zip is a cutting-edge archiver.&#13;
&#13;
Distinctive features:&#13;
&#13;
• High-speed archiving and unpacking.&#13;
• Incorporation of Continuum technology.&#13;
• Ability to decrypt archives using Windows Hello.&#13;
• Play music and video, display images and text files directly in the app.&#13;
• Send files by e-mail, post them on social networks, or share them on OneDrive and DropBox.&#13;
• Select the compression level and password protection.&#13;
• Print documents and images.&#13;
• One purchase gives you a license that is valid for all of your Windows 10 device.&#13;
&#13;
 &#13;
8 Zip knows over 38 languages.&#13;
&#13;
The app has been downloaded more than 8,000,000 times&#13;
&#13;
Thank you for helping to make 8 Zip better! Simply send your suggestions for improvement to 8zip@finebits.com and show your support by giving us a ★★★★★ review.&#13;
&#13;
Technical specifications:&#13;
&#13;
• Create archives: zip, 7z, tar, gzip, bzip2, xz.&#13;
• Open and extract archives: rar, zip, 7z, zipx, iso, bzip2, gzip, tar, arj, cab, cbz, cbr.&#13;
• Built-in viewer and player.&#13;
• View images: jpeg, png, bmp, gif, tiff.&#13;
• Play music: mp3, wma, m4a, aac, wav, ac3.&#13;
• Watch video: avi, 3gp, wmv, mp4, m4v, mov, mkv.&#13;
• Open and view text documents: docx, doc, rtf, txt.&#13;
• Support for the latest archive formats: RAR5 and 7z.&#13;
• Various compression methods: Deflate, Deflate64, BZip, LZMA, PPMd.&#13;
• Create password-protected archives: 256-bit AES encryption.&#13;
• Ability to open encrypted files through Windows Hello and Microsoft Passport technology.&#13;
• Support for decompressing multivolume archives: zip, rar, 7z.&#13;
• Support for Drag&amp;Drop technology.&#13;
• Support for SD cards. &#13;
• Ability to Extract with the application from the Windows Explorer's context menu.&#13;
&#13;
Release notes:&#13;
• It's become easier to create an archive.&#13;
• Archive encryption is now enabled with one click only.&#13;
• Dark and light theme support has been added. Redone all color palettes.&#13;
• UI has been updated with Fluent design.&#13;
• Added new hotkeys.&#13;
• Now you can run multiple instances of the application.&#13;
• Added the ability to open a viewer in a new window. It allows you to look through the images or listen to music without unpacking the archive.&#13;
• 7-zip library updated.&#13;
• The archive navigation has been improved.&#13;
• SVG file support has been added to the built-in viewer.&#13;
&#13;
06/26/2018&#13;
• Ability to Extract with the application from the Windows Explorer's context menu.&#13;
&#13;
12/08/2017&#13;
• 7-Zip library was updated to version 16.04.&#13;
&#13;
05/07/2017&#13;
• Creators Update support.&#13;
• Extended Share contract feature, now you can easily:&#13;
    - send files from archive to the clipboard;&#13;
    - unpack compressed file simple by sending it to 8 Zip from any other app including Explorer;&#13;
    - unpack several archives at once;&#13;
    - compress files with Share from another app including Explorer;&#13;
• Implemented auto update if you modified compressed document in external application.&#13;
• Added option to turn on app window transparency (aka NEON).&#13;
• Added compact overlay mode for image/audio/video viewer (aka Picture in picture).&#13;
• Added equalizer to audio player.&#13;
&#13;
04/14/2017&#13;
• The restoring of original time of files and folders during extraction was added.&#13;
&#13;
10/21/2016&#13;
• Xbox One support.&#13;
• Comic Book Archive support (.cbz, .cbr)&#13;
• UI improvements.&#13;
• New languages: Albanian, Croatian, Estonian, Finnish, Hungarian, Serbian, Swedish.&#13;
&#13;
6/18/2016&#13;
• Improved ability to select items in list for pen and mouse. Now you can do it using selection rectangle.&#13;
&#13;
6/10/2016&#13;
• Integration with Cortana&#13;
&#13;
04/16/2016&#13;
• Basic support of multitasking was added: packing and unpacking of small archives can be performed if app was minimized.&#13;
• Progress bar is shown when archive is opening.&#13;
&#13;
03/18/2016&#13;
8 Zip has become a completely universal UWP app and now works on any Windows 10 device: PC, laptop, tablet, smartphone, Xbox One, Hololens, IoT devices.&#13;
Support has been added for Continuum, Windows Hello, and Microsoft Passport technologies.&#13;
&#13;
12/20/2014&#13;
8 Zip is Universal app from now.&#13;
RAR5 support added.&#13;
Recent archives list.&#13;
New languages: Arabic, Belarusian, Bulgarian, Vietnamese, Greek, Indonesian, Dutch, Polish, Portuguese (Brazil), Romanian, Slovenian, Turkish, Ukrainian, Farsi, Hindi, Czech, Japanese.&#13;
&#13;
09/13/2013&#13;
Advanced compression options&#13;
Built-in viewer&#13;
&#13;
05/16/2013&#13;
In app Language selection&#13;
Translation fixes&#13;
&#13;
05/05/2013&#13;
Slight interface improvements&#13;
A lot of bug fixes&#13;
New live tiles</description><package>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/draydenthemiiyt-maker/10-Store/refs/heads/main/files/24169BooStudio.8Zip_2.1.0.75_x86__4whpyhnstjyn8-1777635785.appx</package><pcCapable>true</pcCapable><mobileCapable>false</mobileCapable><win81compatible>true</win81compatible></app></apps>
</data>
