<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
  <categories>
  </categories>
  <apps>
    <app id="emote-ontrol">
      <name>VAIO Remote Control</name>
      <version>1.1.2.12170 x64</version>
      <icon>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/draydenthemiiyt-maker/10-Store/refs/heads/main/files/apps-1778668785.png</icon>
      <publisher>Sony Corporation</publisher>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <description>For customers using VAIO® with built-in infrared remote control function or optional IR Adapter, you will be able to use this application to control compatible home devices such as TV, set-top box, etc. For customers using optional IR Adapter, please update the device driver from VAIO Update. This infrared remote control app allows you to control various devices; particularly audiovisual devices. Registering a device is simple because the remote control codes for the audiovisual devices of major manufacturers are preset. A registered device can be controlled from your VAIO. Furthermore, gesture controls are supported so you can perform basic operations such as adjusting the volume and changing the channel without even looking at the screen.</description>
      <package>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/draydenthemiiyt-maker/10-Store/refs/heads/main/files/BD9B8345.VAIORemotecontrol_1.1.2.12170_x64__05bme2bjq6sag-1778668779.appx</package>
      <screenshot1>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/draydenthemiiyt-maker/10-Store/refs/heads/main/files/-1778668787.png</screenshot1>
      <pcCapable>true</pcCapable>
      <mobileCapable>false</mobileCapable>
      <win81compatible>true</win81compatible>
    </app>
    <app id="pp-for-indows">
      <name>CNN App for Windows</name>
      <version>1.2.3.0</version>
      <icon>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/draydenthemiiyt-maker/10-Store/refs/heads/main/files/apps.33373.9007199266245764.0ba407dd-2796-4551-9fb7-e1e39a3b36eb-1778670653.png</icon>
      <publisher>CNN INTERACTIVE GROUP, Inc.</publisher>
      <featured>false</featured>
      <description>CNN connects you to the world, wherever you are. Stay informed with the latest headlines and original stories from around the globe. Follow up-to-the-minute reporting with breaking news and video. Lead the conversation by sharing today’s news and dig deeper into the stories that matter most to you. • Get breaking news and follow stories as they develop. • Go beyond the surface with international, politics, opinion, tech and entertainment stories and more. • Contribute your story or opinion to CNN iReport by uploading photos and video directly from your app. Follow other iReporters and see stories from their point of view. • Read the top headlines on the go with the CNN Live Tile. • Choose the font size that most appeals to you. Have questions or feedback on the CNN App? E-mail us at WindowsTablet@cnn.com. We are always looking for suggestions on how to provide the best experience possible for you.</description>
      <package>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/draydenthemiiyt-maker/10-Store/refs/heads/main/files/588E6FFA.CNNAppforWindows_1.2.3.0_neutral__cs8eyncph15zy-1778670650.appx</package>
      <screenshot1>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/draydenthemiiyt-maker/10-Store/refs/heads/main/files/Screenshot-1-1778670654.png</screenshot1>
      <screenshot2>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/draydenthemiiyt-maker/10-Store/refs/heads/main/files/Screenshot-2-1778670655.png</screenshot2>
      <screenshot3>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/draydenthemiiyt-maker/10-Store/refs/heads/main/files/Screenshot-3-1778670656.png</screenshot3>
      <screenshot4>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/draydenthemiiyt-maker/10-Store/refs/heads/main/files/Screenshot-4-1778670658.png</screenshot4>
      <pcCapable>true</pcCapable>
      <mobileCapable>false</mobileCapable>
      <win81compatible>true</win81compatible>
    </app>
  </apps>
</data>
