<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
  <categories>
  </categories>
  <apps>
  <app id="espicable-e-inion-ush"><name>Despicable Me: Minion Rush</name><version>4.1.4.1</version><icon>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/draydenthemiiyt-maker/10-Store/refs/heads/main/files/59857_Despicable_me_Minion_Rush-1778068188.jpg</icon><publisher>GAMELOFT SA</publisher><featured>false</featured><description>This game allows multiplayer play and is not subject to Xbox Live Family Settings. Microsoft shares User IDs and gamertags.&#13;
&#13;
****** JOIN 750 MILLION PLAYERS WORLDWIDE! *****&#13;
&#13;
Race with the Minions in the award-winning fan-favourite endless runner, Despicable Me: Minion Rush! Collect bananas as you jump, roll, dodge and scramble against others in fun-filled, fast-paced missions! Run as Carl, Jerry and Dave, get awesome costumes, play exciting mini-games and explore locations inspired by the Despicable Me movies!&#13;
&#13;
ALL THE FUN OF DESPICABLE ME!&#13;
• Run through iconic locations from the movie and discover secret areas&#13;
• Enjoy unexpected Minion moments, like becoming a MEGA MINION and riding the FLUFFY UNICORN or GRU’S ROCKET&#13;
• Use hilarious weapons and power-ups while competing with other players in Minion Races&#13;
• Battle exclusive villains such as Vector, El Macho and the Villaintriloquist&#13;
• Experience original animations, voice-overs and state-of-the-art 3D graphics created just for the game&#13;
&#13;
______________________________________________&#13;
&#13;
You can download and play this game for free. Please be informed that it also allows you to play using virtual currency, which can be acquired as you progress through the game, or by deciding to watch certain advertisements, or paying with real money. In-app purchases range from £0.79 to £38.59. You can disable in-app purchases by adjusting your device’s settings.&#13;
&#13;
Languages: English, Arabic, French, German, Indonesian, Italian, Japanese, Korean, Portuguese, Russian, Simplified Chinese, Spanish, Thai, Traditional Chinese, Turkish&#13;
&#13;
An additional download of 50 to 150 MB is required to play this game. Please note the size of this required download may change without notice.&#13;
&#13;
The game requires an Internet connection (3G or Wi-Fi) for download and updates, and other features including playing with friends, making in-app purchases and watching advertisements.&#13;
&#13;
Certain aspects of this game, such as collaborating with, playing against or sharing in-game items with other players will require the player to connect to a social network like Facebook. Please note this connection is never compulsory to progress through the game. These features may be disabled in certain countries.&#13;
&#13;
This game may contain third-party advertisements that will redirect you to a third-party site. You can disable your device’s ad identifier being used for interest-based advertising in the settings menu of your device. This option can be found in PC Settings -&gt; Privacy -&gt; General.&#13;
___________________________________________________________________________________________&#13;
&#13;
Visit our official site at http://www.gameloft.com&#13;
Follow us on Twitter at http://glft.co/GameloftonTwitter or like us on Facebook at http://facebook.com/Gameloft to get more info about all our upcoming titles.&#13;
Check out our videos and game trailers on http://www.youtube.com/Gameloft &#13;
Discover our blog at http://glft.co/Gameloft_Official_Blog for the inside scoop on everything Gameloft.&#13;
&#13;
Privacy Policy: http://www.gameloft.co.uk/privacy-notice/&#13;
Terms of Use: http://www.gameloft.co.uk/conditions/&#13;
End-User License Agreement: http://www.gameloft.com/eula/?lang=en&#13;
&#13;
If you install this game, you understand and agree that Microsoft may share your User ID and gamertag with the game publisher to enable game features. This game includes multiplayer features with online interactions that are not subject to Xbox Live Family Settings. These features may include the following interactions with other players online:&#13;
&#13;
• Send and receive game invites;&#13;
• Play cooperatively or head-to-head;&#13;
• Send and receive in-game text messages;&#13;
• Communicate via in-game voice chat.&#13;
&#13;
Please see the publisher’s site http://www.gameloft.com/privacy-notice/windows/ for information on settings it may enable.</description><package>https://archive.org/download/minionrushwin8_202503/GAMELOFTSA.DespicableMeMinionRush_0pp20fcewvvtj.zip/GAMELOFTSA.DespicableMeMinionRush_0pp20fcewvvtj%2FGAMELOFTSA.DespicableMeMinionRush_4.1.4.1_x86__0pp20fcewvvtj.Appx</package><screenshot1>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/draydenthemiiyt-maker/10-Store/refs/heads/main/files/minionrush_screenshot1-1778068189.png</screenshot1><screenshot2>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/draydenthemiiyt-maker/10-Store/refs/heads/main/files/minionrush_screenshot2-1778068191.png</screenshot2><screenshot3>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/draydenthemiiyt-maker/10-Store/refs/heads/main/files/minionrush_screenshot3-1778068192.png</screenshot3><screenshot4>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/draydenthemiiyt-maker/10-Store/refs/heads/main/files/minionrush_screenshot4-1778068194.png</screenshot4><screenshot5>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/draydenthemiiyt-maker/10-Store/refs/heads/main/files/minionrush_screenshot5-1778068195.png</screenshot5><pcCapable>true</pcCapable><mobileCapable>false</mobileCapable><win81compatible>true</win81compatible></app></apps>
</data>
