<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<data>
  <categories>
  </categories>
  <apps>
  <app id="ank-f-merica"><name>Bank Of America</name><version>1.7.0.0</version><icon>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/draydenthemiiyt-maker/10-Store/refs/heads/main/files/IMG_2175-1779482920.png</icon><publisher>Bank Of America</publisher><featured>false</featured><description>IMPORTANT: In early March 2015, we’ll no longer support this app for this device. We’re sorry for the inconvenience. You can access mobile banking with us through your browser. Just go to www.bankofamerica.com. Bank conveniently and securely with Bank of America® Mobile Banking. Our Windows® 8 app makes it easier than ever. Manage Your Accounts* • Check activity and balances in checking, savings and credit card accounts • View mortgage and loan balances • View Merrill Edge and Merrill Lynch investment accounts • Set app Alerts to be notified of important account and security info Send Money to Virtually Anyone* • Securely send and receive money using a mobile number or email address (including to and from U.S. accounts outside of Bank of America)1 • Add recipients for email/mobile number transfers • Manage transfers between your Bank of America accounts • Visit www.bankofamerica.com/easymoneytransfer to learn more Pay Bills* • Schedule, edit or cancel payments • Pay eBills Deposit Checks • Use our app to snap photos of checks and deposit them from your mobile device2 • View processing deposits in account details in the app Enjoy BankAmeriDeals® • Choose Deals, shop as you normally do with your credit/debit cards and receive cash back • Get cash back into your eligible Bank of America account3 Stay Secure* • Sign in safely, using your same Online Banking credentials • Use SafePass® for additional security during sensitive transactions (you’ll receive a code to verify your identity) Contact Us Easily • Call us with any questions • Find ATMs and banking centers *Please visit Online Banking for these banking needs: Enrolling in Online Banking; wire transfers; transfers to external banks; transfers from credit cards; ordering new checks; ordering check copies; updating account nickname/transaction descriptions; canceling recurring transfers and payments; enrolling in Bill Pay/managing eBill information; changing or retrieving Online IDs; resetting Passcodes; unlocking/resetting SiteKey; stopping checks; ordering replacement debit or credit cards; activating new debit cards; setting travel flags; using ShopSafe®; going paperless; viewing mortgage and loan account details; enrolling in SafePass. 1Enrollment and Bank of America checking/savings account required. No fee for this service; dollar/frequency limits apply. Transfer permitted only to U.S.-based consumer accounts. See Online Banking Service Agreement for details. 2Deposits subject to verification and not available for immediate withdrawal. See Terms for other restrictions. 3Earned cash back credited the month following redemption. See Terms for other restrictions. Having general app issues? • Try clearing the browser and BofA app cache, then power off the device • If you’re on your home WiFi network and have a problem connecting, try resetting your modem/router • Make sure you’re running the latest OS • Visit our in-app Help to learn more Terms/Service Agreement: www.bankofamerica.com/serviceagreement Windows® is a trademark of the Microsoft group of companies. Bank of America and related trademarks are trademarks of Bank of America Corporation Bank of America, N.A. Member FDIC © 2015 Bank of America Corporation</description><package>https://files.catbox.moe/t7h945.AppxBundle</package><screenshot1>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/draydenthemiiyt-maker/10-Store/refs/heads/main/files/bank1-1779482921.png</screenshot1><screenshot2>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/draydenthemiiyt-maker/10-Store/refs/heads/main/files/bank2-1779482923.png</screenshot2><screenshot3>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/draydenthemiiyt-maker/10-Store/refs/heads/main/files/bank3-1779482924.png</screenshot3><screenshot4>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/draydenthemiiyt-maker/10-Store/refs/heads/main/files/bank4-1779482926.png</screenshot4><screenshot5>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/draydenthemiiyt-maker/10-Store/refs/heads/main/files/bank5-1779482928.png</screenshot5><pcCapable>true</pcCapable><mobileCapable>false</mobileCapable><win81compatible>false</win81compatible></app></apps>
</data>
